<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<LanguageData>

	<!-- Initial Page UI -->
	<SkillPassionPageTitle>Determine Backstories and Traits</SkillPassionPageTitle>
	<SkillPassionSkillSelectWidgetLabel>Group Passions For Each Skill</SkillPassionSkillSelectWidgetLabel>
	<SkillPassionPawnBiology>Biological Settings</SkillPassionPawnBiology>
	<SkillPassionUsable>Useable:</SkillPassionUsable>

	<SkillPassionAgeRangeLabel>Adults Will Have an Age Between {0} Years</SkillPassionAgeRangeLabel>
	<SkillPassionMelaninRangeLabel>Skin Color Variation</SkillPassionMelaninRangeLabel>
	<SkillPassionSkillControls>Backstory and Passion Settings</SkillPassionSkillControls>
	<SkillPassionSkillVariationLevel>Vary Skill Weights By 100%-{0} For Backstory Variety</SkillPassionSkillVariationLevel>
	<SkillPassionPassionMaxLabel>Max "Passion Points" in Generating Pawns {0}</SkillPassionPassionMaxLabel>
	<SkillPassionGroupwideLabel>The groupwide skill requirements make up {0} of possible passion points.</SkillPassionGroupwideLabel>
	<!-- Scale these up or down according to the how long your language is -->
	<!-- For English, this is scaled so that "Construction" is one line for the former and there is a comfy even margin for the row length. -->
	<SkillPassionSkillTextLength>85</SkillPassionSkillTextLength>
	<SkillPassionSkillSelectWidgetOverallLength>490</SkillPassionSkillSelectWidgetOverallLength>

	<SkillPassionTraitBackstory>This trait is forced by the given backstory of the pawn. Locked pawns will not have this trait removed for trait options, and unlocked pawns may reroll a different backstory to avoid this trait if chosen traits conflict with it.</SkillPassionTraitBackstory>
	<SkillPassionTraitPlayerChosen>This trait is being locked in on request. Click this trait to remove the lock in for this pawn slot.</SkillPassionTraitPlayerChosen>
	<ClickOnPawnToCustomizeSkills>Click For Skill Loadout UI</ClickOnPawnToCustomizeSkills>

	<VariationTooltip>Procedural generation will try to pick pawn backstories and simulate randomization to quickly arrive at a certain loadout of passions. It does so by attaching a weight for each skill and picking stories by the best weight.\n\nVarying this weight by a random amount on generation gives more backstory variety and can help get out of ruts without having to specify each weight to get a specific story combination.</VariationTooltip>

	<PassionPointsDescriptionTooltip>When characters are generated, they are given a range of points between 0-9, based on a normal distribution centered at five points. Outliers on the far ends (i.e. exactly 0 or 9) are exceedingly unlikely.\n\n    - Minor passions take 1 point\n    - Major passions take 1.5 points\n\nCertain traits can force or prevent passions, but otherwise a set amount of major and minor passions are given based on the skill level for the pawn generated.</PassionPointsDescriptionTooltip>

	<WarnUnsatisfiedSkills>Pawn generation was not able to satisfy the following requirements with the given passions per pawn:\n\n{0}\nThis can be fixed by lowering some skill/passion requirements or increasing the passions each pawn can have.\n\nDo you wish to continue anyways?</WarnUnsatisfiedSkills>
	<LockedPawnButtonDescription>This pawn is locked in and will not be randomized or changed in any way by the procedural editor.\n\nClick to unlock.</LockedPawnButtonDescription>
	<UnlockedPawnButtonDescription>This pawn is not locked in and will be randomized as needed by the procedural editor to fit other requests.\n\nClick to lock.</UnlockedPawnButtonDescription>
	<ClickToCustomizeGeneration>Click to customize this pawn slot a bit more.</ClickToCustomizeGeneration>
</LanguageData>